addynamo.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy - Ad Dynamo

Privacy matters to us.  We will respect your privacy at all times.

**1\. Introduction**

1.1 Set out below are details about the Privacy Policy which applies to the www.addynamo.co.za website (“Website”), which is owned and operated by Ad Dynamo International (Pty) Ltd, Registration Number 2008/024727/07 (“Ad Dynamo”) and which Privacy Policy forms part of the terms and conditions pertaining to the access and use of the Website.  
1.2 We respect and take your privacy seriously, and as such we will use and process the personal information that we collect from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please be aware that we collect and process your personal information for lawful purposes which are related to the functions and business activities of Ad Dynamo, which is the owner of the Website, and that such purposes are compatible with and necessary in order for us to pursue and maintain the legitimate interests of Ad Dynamo.  
1.3 We urge you to take the time to carefully read our entire Privacy Policy for complete detail about our privacy practices and your personal information.

**2\. What we mean by Personal Information**

2.1 When we refer to “Personal Information” in this Policy, we mean information that we can use to contact you or identify you as an individual or is capable of identifying you. By personal information we don’t mean general, statistical, aggregated or anonymous information.  
2.2 You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of any Personal Information that you submit to us. Inaccurate information may affect your experience when using the Website and related tools and applications, and our ability to contact you as described in this Privacy Policy.

**3\. Consent**

3.1 Your accessing of our Website, and/use of our services, signifies that you give your consent to us to collect, process and use Personal Information about you as specified below, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**4\. Information Collected About You**

4.1 We undertake not to collect and process your Personal Information in anyway, except for the purposes of our newsletters.  
4.2 We will always clearly communicate that you are opting in for further communication.  
4.3  An obvious opt out process will be available at all times to unsubscribe from our mailing lists.4.4.  
4.4. Your information will never be shared with any third party, and all data processors (in terms of GDPR) are bound to a Data Processing Agreement and strict GDPR legislation.  
4.5 You have the right at any time to request that we confirm the Personal Information which we hold about you, and to request that we correct any incorrect or inaccurate Personal Information which we hold about you, or to delete your Personal Information completely.

**5\. How Do We Secure and Retain Your Information**

5.1 We restrict internal access to the Personal Information that we collect from you to our authorized team members only.  
5.2 We will always endeavour to secure the integrity and confidentiality of your Personal Information which is in our possession or under our control, and to this end we have put in place technical, physical, and administrative safeguards to protect the Personal Information that we collect.  
5.3 If your personal information is compromised in any way, you will be notified within 24 hours.  
5.4 The time periods for which we keep your Personal Information may vary according to the use or purpose attached to the Personal Information. Unless there is a specific legal requirement requiring us to keep your Personal Information, we will not keep it for longer than necessary for the purpose for which the Personal Information was collected or for which it is to be processed.

**6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

6.1 We reserve the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy or any of our tools or services at any time and any changes will be effective upon being posted unless we advise otherwise.  If we make any material changes to this policy we will notify you by email (sent to the email address which you have provided to us) and/or by means of a notice on this Website prior to the change becoming effective.  
6.2 We encourage you to periodically review this Website for the latest information on our privacy practices. If you do not accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, we ask that you do not use the Website. Please exit the Website immediately if you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**7\. Regulatory establishments**

7.1 Ad Dynamo complies with the collection of data/ usage practices and targeting of ads in accordance with to the following self-regulatory establishments:

7.2.1 NAI Self-Regulatory Code of Conduct for Online Behavioural Advertising (www.networkadvertising.org); and  
7.2.2 IAB UK Good Practice Principles for Online Behavioural Advertising (www.iab.net/guidelines)

7.3 Ad Dynamo complies fully with GDPR regulations.

**8\. Contact Us**

Please send us an email using the Contact Us link of our Website if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Personal Information we maintain about you.

**9\. Complaints**

If you are not satisfied with the way in which we process your Personal Information, you may lodge a complaint with your information regulator.
